<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | Alex XU</title>
    <link>https://www.alexxu.me/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://www.alexxu.me/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.alexxu.me/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.alexxu.me/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced American Sign Language Recognition System</title>
      <link>https://www.alexxu.me/project/asl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.alexxu.me/project/asl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The wearable device based sign language recognition system plays a crucial role in the daily communication between people with disabilities and other ordinary people. A product that can quickly configure and accurately translate words is the goal people pursue. However, the current products or scientific research projects in related fields have more or fewer shortcomings, either because the customer samples that need to be collected are too complicated and the configuration time is too long, or because they only focus on a specific step for improvement. This project aims to study the common problems of existing products and improve sign language recognition system performance on wearable devices through our analysis and improvement measures. Finally, a complete set of end-to-end sign language recognition systems will be developed on smartphones or related devices, hoping to provide greater convenience to the daily life of people with disabilities in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhomboid Wing Technology Demonstrator based on Stealth Design</title>
      <link>https://www.alexxu.me/project/rhomboid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.alexxu.me/project/rhomboid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Awards:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The First Award in 28th &amp;ldquo;Feng Ru Cup&amp;rdquo; Beihang University&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outstanding Student Award of the 17th Beijing Youth Science and Technology Reserve Talents Early Training Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Bonding Technology</title>
      <link>https://www.alexxu.me/project/nims/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.alexxu.me/project/nims/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tried out &amp;ldquo;Surface Activated Bonding&amp;rdquo; related technology, and personally carried out hands-on operation in the super-clean laboratory under the guidance of Prof. Akitsu Shigetou. Comment on potential areas for improvement within my capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
